<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bliss Football</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_club">Club Football</string>
    <string name="title_international">International Football</string>
    <string name="legends">Know Your Legends</string>
    <string name="coaches">Know Your Coaches</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="todo1">TODO1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_legends">Legends</string>
    <string name="epl">English Premier League</string>
    <string name="laliga">La Liga</string>
    <string name="seriea">Serie A</string>
    <string name="ligue1">Ligue 1</string>
    <string name="bundesliga">Bundesliga</string>
    <string name="uefa">Union of European Football Associations</string>
    <string name="concacaf">The Confederation of North, Central American and Caribbean Association Football</string>
    <string name="uefa1">UEFA</string>
    <string name="concacaf1">CONCACAF</string>
    <string name="epl1">EPL</string>
    <string name="coaches1">Coaches</string>
    <string name="legends1">Legends</string>
    <string name="countriesUEFA">Countries Associated with UEFA</string>
    <string name="countriesCONCACAF">Countries Associated with CONCACAF</string>
    <string name="austriaDescription">The Austria national football team (German: Österreichische Fußballnationalmannschaft) is the association football team that represents Austria in international competition and is controlled by the Austrian Football Association (German: Österreichischer Fußballbund). Austria has qualified for seven FIFA World Cups, most recently in 1998. The country played in the UEFA European Championship
        for the first time in 2008, when it co-hosted the event with Switzerland, and most recently qualified in 2016.</string>
    <string name="canadaDescription">The Canada men\'s national soccer team (French: Équipe du Canada de soccer masculin) represents Canada in international soccer competitions at
        the senior men\'s level officially since 1924. They are overseen by the Canadian Soccer Association and compete in the Confederation of North
        , Central American and Caribbean Association Football (CONCACAF).Their most significant achievements are winning the 1985 CONCACAF
        Championship to qualify for the 1986 FIFA World Cup[4] and winning the 2000 CONCACAF Gold Cup to qualify for the 2001 FIFA Confederations Cup.[5] Canada is the only national team to win a Gold Cup aside from regional powerhouses Mexico and the United States.[6] Canada also won a gold medal in the 1904 Summer Olympics.[7] The 1986 World Cup was their only successful qualification campaign in their history.</string>


    <string name="belgiumDescription">The Belgian national football team[C] has officially represented Belgium in association football since their maiden match in 1904. The squad is under the global jurisdiction of FIFA and is governed in Europe by UEFA—both of which were co-founded by the Belgian team\'s supervising body, the Royal Belgian Football Association (RBFA). Periods of regular Belgian representation at the highest international level, from 1920 to 1938, from 1982 to 2002 and again from 2014 onwards, have alternated with mostly unsuccessful qualification rounds. Most of Belgium\'s home matches are played at the King Baudouin Stadium in Brussels.

Belgium\'s national team have participated in three quadrennial major football competitions. It appeared in the end stages of thirteen FIFA World Cups and five UEFA European Championships, and featured at three Olympic football tournaments, including the 1920 Olympic tournament which they won. Other notable performances are victories over four reigning world champions—West Germany, Brazil, Argentina and France—between 1954 and 2002. Belgium has long-standing football rivalries with its Dutch and French counterparts, having played both teams nearly every year from 1905 to 1967. The squad has been known as the Red Devils since 1906; its fan club is named "1895".

During the national player career of forward Paul Van Himst, the most-praised Belgian footballer of the 20th century, Belgium took third place at Euro 1972. After that, they experienced two golden ages with many gifted players. In the first period, which lasted from the 1980s to the early 1990s, the team finished as runners-up at Euro 1980 and fourth in the 1986 World Cup. In the second, under guidance of Marc Wilmots and later Roberto Martínez in the 2010s, Belgium topped the FIFA World Rankings for the first time in November 2015 and finished third at the 2018 World Cup. Belgium currently participates in League A of the first UEFA Nations League edition.</string>

    <string name="franceDescription">The France national football team (French: Équipe de France de football) represents France in international
        football and is controlled by the French Football Federation, also known as FFF, or in French: Fédération française de football.
        The team\'s colours are blue, white and red, and the coq gaulois its symbol. France are colloquially known as Les Bleus (The Blues).
        The French side are the reigning World Cup holders, having won the 2018 FIFA World Cup on 15 July 2018.
        France play home matches at the Stade de France in Saint-Denis, Paris, and their manager is Didier Deschamps.
        They have won two FIFA World Cups, two UEFA European Championships, two FIFA Confederations Cups and one Olympic tournament.
        France experienced much of its success in four major eras: in the 1950s, 1980s, late 1990s/early 2000s, and mid/late 2010s, respectively,
        which resulted in numerous major honours. France was one of the four European teams that participated in the inaugural World Cup in 1930
        and, although having been eliminated in the qualification stage six times, is one of only three teams that have entered every World Cup
        qualifying cycle.In 1958, the team, led by Raymond Kopa and Just Fontaine, finished in third place at the FIFA World Cup.
        In 1984, France, led by Ballon d\'Or winner Michel Platini, won UEFA Euro 1984 and Football at the 1984 Summer Olympics.
        Under the captaincy of Didier Deschamps and three-time FIFA World Player of the Year Zinedine Zidane, France won the FIFA World Cup in 1998.
        Two years later, the team triumphed at UEFA Euro 2000. France won the FIFA Confederations Cup in 2001 and 2003, and reached the 2006
        FIFA World Cup final, which it lost 5–3 on penalties to Italy. The team also reached the final of UEFA Euro 2016, where they lost 1–0 to
        Portugal in extra time. France won the 2018 FIFA World Cup, defeating Croatia 4–2 in the final match on 15 July 2018.
        This was the second time they had won the tournament after winning it on home soil in 1998.
        France was the first national team that has won the three most important men\'s titles recognized by FIFA: the World Cup, the Confederations Cup, and the Olympic tournament after victory in the Confederations Cup in 2001. Since 2001, Argentina (after the 2004 Olympics) and Brazil (after the 2016 Olympics) are the other two national teams that have won these three titles. They have also won their respective continental championship (Copa América for Argentina and Brazil, and UEFA European Championship for France).</string>

    <string name="germanyDescription">The Germany national football team (German: deutsche Fußballnationalmannschaft or Die Mannschaft) is the men\'s football team that has represented Germany in international competition since 1908.[6] It is governed by the German Football Association (Deutscher Fußball-Bund), founded in 1900.[10][11] Ever since the DFB was reinaugurated in 1949 the team has represented the Federal Republic of Germany. Under Allied occupation and division, two other separate national teams were also recognised by FIFA: the Saarland team representing the Saarland (1950–1956) and the East German team representing the German Democratic Republic (1952–1990). Both have been absorbed along with their records[12][13] by the current national team. The official name and code "Germany FR (FRG)" was shortened to "Germany (GER)" following the reunification in 1990.

Germany is one of the most successful national teams in international competitions, having won four World Cups (1954, 1974, 1990, 2014), three European Championships (1972, 1980, 1996), and one Confederations Cup (2017).[10] They have also been runners-up three times in the European Championships, four times in the World Cup, and a further four third-place finishes at World Cups.[10] East Germany won Olympic Gold in 1976.[14]

Germany is the only nation to have won both the FIFA World Cup and the FIFA Women\'s World Cup.[15][16]

At the end of the 2014 World Cup, Germany earned the highest Elo rating of any national football team in history, with a record 2205 points.[17] Germany is also the only European nation that has won a FIFA World Cup in the Americas. The manager of the national team is Joachim Löw.</string>

    <string name="irelandDescription">The Republic of Ireland national football team (Irish: Foireann peile náisiúnta Phoblacht na hÉireann) represents Ireland in association football. It is governed by the Football Association of Ireland (FAI) and stages its home fixtures at the Aviva Stadium in Dublin.

The team made their debut at the 1924 Summer Olympics, reaching the quarter-finals. Between 1924 and 1936, the team competed as the Irish Free State and from then until 1950, it was referred to by the FAI as Éire or Ireland. In 1953, FIFA decreed that for competitive matches in tournaments that both Irish teams may enter, the FAI team would be officially called the Republic of Ireland while the IFA team was to be named Northern Ireland.[5] Northern Ireland was allowed to use the title Ireland by FIFA in the Home International Competition until it was discontinued in 1984. The Republic of Ireland was the first nation from outside the United Kingdom to defeat England at home at a fixture played at Goodison Park, Liverpool, in 1949. The team also reached the quarter-final stage of the 1964 European Nations\' Cup, where they lost to the eventual winners Spain.

Under the guidance of Jack Charlton, the team enjoyed its most successful era, reaching their highest FIFA world ranking ever at sixth in August 1993, and qualifying for UEFA Euro 1988 in their first appearance at the UEFA European Championship, reaching the quarter-finals of the 1990 FIFA World Cup in their first ever appearance at the finals, as well as making the last 16 at the 1994 edition. Charlton\'s successor Mick McCarthy lost out on the next two major tournaments but ultimately qualified for the 2002 World Cup, making it to the last 16. Under Giovanni Trapattoni, the team narrowly lost out on qualification for the 2010 World Cup during a controversial play-off, but went on to qualify for Euro 2012.

The team failed to qualify for the 2014 World Cup in Brazil, marking the end of Trapattoni\'s tenure as manager. The Republic of Ireland also fell to a record low FIFA ranking of 59th, then a record low of 70th in June 2014.[6] For the next Euro qualifying campaign under manager Martin O\'Neill, the Republic of Ireland finished third behind Germany and Poland, but went on to qualify for Euro 2016 after a 3–1 aggregate win over Bosnia and Herzegovina in the play-offs. The Boys in Green reached the Round of 16 stage at that tournament and were knocked out by the hosts and eventual runners-up France after losing 2–1.</string>

    <string name="netherlandDescription">The Netherlands national football team[B] has officially represented the Netherlands in international football since its initial match in 1905. The national team is controlled by the Royal Dutch Football Association (KNVB), which is a part of UEFA, and under the jurisdiction of FIFA the governing body for football in the Netherlands. Most of the Netherlands\' home matches are played at the Johan Cruyff Arena and the Stadion Feijenoord. The team is colloquially referred to as Het Nederlands Elftal (The Dutch Eleven) or the Oranje, after the House of Orange-Nassau. Like the country itself, the team is sometimes (also colloquially) referred to as Holland. The fan club is known as the "Het Legioen".[8]

The Netherlands has competed in ten FIFA World Cups, appearing in the finals three times (in 1974, 1978 and 2010). They have also appeared in nine UEFA European Championships winning the 1988 tournament in West Germany. Additionally, the team won a bronze medal at the Olympic football event in 1908, 1912 and 1920. The Netherlands has long-standing football rivalries with neighbors Belgium and Germany.</string>

    <string name="russiaDescription">The Russia national football team (Russian: национа́льная сбо́рная Росси́и по футбо́лу, natsionálnaya sbórnaya Rossii po futbólu) represents Russia in association football and is controlled by the Russian Football Union (Russian: Российский Футбольный Союз, Rossiyskiy Futboľnyj Soyuz), the governing body for football in Russia. Russia is a member of UEFA, they won the first edition of the respective continental competition in 1960 as the Soviet Union (of which Russia is the successor).[4]

Russia\'s home ground is the Luzhniki Stadium in Moscow and their current head coach is Stanislav Cherchesov.</string>

    <string name="portugalDescription">The Portugal national football team (Portuguese: Seleção Portuguesa de Futebol, pronounced [sɨlɛˈsɐ̃w̃ puɾtuˈgezɐ dɨ futɨˈbɔl]) represents Portugal in international men\'s association football competition since 1921. It is controlled by the Portuguese Football Federation, the governing body for football in Portugal.

Portugal\'s first participation in a major tournament finals was at the 1966 World Cup, saw a team featuring famed striker Eusébio finish in third place. The next two times Portugal qualified for the World Cup finals were in 1986 and 2002, going out in the first round both times. Portugal also made it to the semi-finals of the UEFA Euro 1984 final tournament, losing 3–2 after extra time to the hosts and eventual winners France. The team reached the semi-finals of Euro 2000, the 2006 World Cup and Euro 2012, as well as the final of Euro 2004, the latter on home soil. At Euro 2016, Portugal won its first ever major trophy, defeating hosts France 1–0 after extra time, with the winning goal scored by Eder. With the win, Portugal qualified and made its first appearance in the FIFA Confederations Cup held in Russia, where they finished third.

The team\'s home stadium is the Estádio Nacional, in Oeiras, although most of their home games are frequently played in other stadiums across the country. The current head coach is Fernando Santos and the captain is Cristiano Ronaldo, who also holds the team record for most caps and for most goals.</string>

    <string name="spainDescription">Spain national football team (Spanish: Selección de fútbol de España) is the national football team of Spain. The current head coach is Luis Enrique. The team is often called La Roja ("The Red [One]"), La Furia Roja ("The Red Fury"), La Furia Española ("The Spanish Fury") or just La Furia ("The Fury"). The Spanish team became a member of FIFA in 1904, even though the team was made in 1909. Spain had their first match on the 8th of August of 1920 against Denmark. Since the team\'s creation in 1909, they have been in 13 FIFA World Cups, and 9 UEFA European Football Championships.

Spain are three-time European champions, having won the UEFA Euro 2012, UEFA Euro 2008, and 1964 European Championship. From November 2006 through June 2009 Spain went undefeated for 35 matches, a record shared with Brazil. Spain are one of the eight national teams to have won the FIFA World Cup; they won their first at the 2010 World Cup in South Africa when they defeated the Netherlands 1–0 after extra time. Andrés Iniesta scored the winning goal in the 116th minute.

The team\'s achievements have led to many commentators and football experts naming them one of the best international sides in football history.</string>

    <string name="switzerlandDescription">The Switzerland national football team (German: Schweizer Fußballnationalmannschaft, French: Équipe de Suisse de football, Italian: Nazionale di calcio della Svizzera, Romansh: Squadra naziunala da ballape da la Svizra) is the national football team of Switzerland. The team is controlled by the Swiss Football Association.

Switzerland\'s best ever performance at the FIFA World Cup are three quarter-final appearances, in 1934, 1938 and 1954. They hosted the competition in 1954, where they played with Austria in the quarter-final match, losing 7–5, which today still stands as the highest scoring ever World Cup match.[4] At the 2006 FIFA World Cup, Switzerland set a FIFA World Cup record by being eliminated from the tournament despite not conceding a single goal, being eliminated by Ukraine in a penalty shootout in the round of sixteen; failing to score a single penalty, thus becoming the first nation to do so.[5] They didn\'t concede a goal until a match against Chile at the 2010 FIFA World Cup, conceding in the 75th minute; setting a World Cup finals record for consecutive minutes without conceding a goal.[6]

Switzerland and Austria were the co-hosts of UEFA Euro 2008, where the Swiss made their third appearance in the competition, but didn\'t progress from the group stage for the third time.[7][8]

Overall, Switzerland\'s best ever result at an official football competition was the silver medal they earned in 1924, after losing to Uruguay 3–0 in the final of the 1924 Olympic Games.[9]</string>

    <string name="turkeyDescription">The Turkey national football team (Turkish: Türkiye Millî Futbol Takımı) represents Turkey in association football and is controlled by the Turkish Football Federation, the governing body for football in Turkey. They are affiliated with UEFA.

Turkey has qualified three times for the FIFA World Cup, in 1950, 1954, and 2002, although they withdrew from the 1950 event. Turkey has also qualified four times for the UEFA European Championship, in 1996, 2000, 2008, and 2016. They have reached the semi-finals of three major tournaments: the 2002 World Cup, the 2003 FIFA Confederations Cup, and Euro 2008. After their third-place finish at the 2002 World Cup, which marked a high point in Turkish football history, Turkey occupied a spot in the top ten of the FIFA World Rankings for the first time since the rankings were introduced in December 1992.[7]</string>

    <string name="ukrainDescription">The Ukraine national football team (Ukrainian: збірна України з футболу) is the national football team of Ukraine and is controlled by the Football Federation of Ukraine. After Ukrainian Independence and the country\'s breakaway from the Soviet Union, they played their first match against Hungary on 29 April 1992. The team\'s biggest success on the world stage was reaching the quarter-finals in the 2006 FIFA World Cup, which also marked the team\'s debut in the finals of a major championship.[4] As the host nation, Ukraine automatically qualified for UEFA Euro 2012.[4] Four years later, Ukraine qualified for Euro 2016 via the play-off route, the first time qualifying for a UEFA European Championship via the qualifying process, as it finished in third place in its qualifying group. This marked the first time in Ukraine\'s five play-off appearances that it managed to win such a tie, previously having been unsuccessful in the play-off ties for the Euro 2000, 2002 World Cup, 2010 World Cup and 2014 World Cup.

Ukraine\'s home ground is the Olimpiyskiy Stadium in Kiev.</string>

    <string name="costaricaDescription">The Costa Rica national football team (Spanish: Selección de fútbol de Costa Rica) is administered by the Costa Rican Football Federation (FEDEFUTBOL), the governing body for football in Costa Rica. They have been a member of the International Federation of Association Football (FIFA) since 1927, a member of the Confederation of North, Central American and Caribbean Association Football (CONCACAF) since 1961, and a member of the Central American Football Union (UNCAF) since 1990.

Costa Rica is the most successful national football team in the history of Central America. They have won three CONCACAF Championships (1963, 1969 and 1989) and a leading with eight championships in the Copa Centroamericana and its predecessor. Costa Rica is the only national team in Central America to have played in four FIFA World Cup editions. Costa Rica\'s national football team has the all-time highest average Football Elo Ranking in Central America with 1597.1, and the all-time highest Football Elo Ranking in Central America, with 1806 in 2014.

Since the late 1980s, the team has continuously been visible as a solidly competitive side, with a prominent performance in the 1990 FIFA World Cup in Italy, making it to the knockout stage in their debut after finishing second in their group during the first phase, below Brazil. They also managed to qualify for the 2002 and 2006 FIFA World Cups. In 2014, Costa Rica made their best performance in history by finishing first in their group that consisted of three former World Cup champions: Uruguay, Italy, and England. During the Round of 16 they defeated Greece 5–3 via a penalty shootout after a 1–1 draw. Reaching the quarterfinals for their very first time the "Ticos" were defeated by the Netherlands also in a penalty shootout (3–4) after a scoreless draw on 5 July.</string>




</resources>
